Guide to Boston College Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00209
Cubberley Education Library
Boston College
1868-1980
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00209
197 item(s) Catalogs for 1868/69, 1870/71-1872/73, 1874/75, 1890/91, 1900/01, 1902/03, 1904/05, 1922, 1924/25, 1926/27-1928/29, 1930-1945, 1953/54-1966/67, 1973/74-1979/80
Located in Chestnut Hill, Mass. Founded in 1863 by the Jesuits in Boston, Mass.
Massachusetts; Catholic universities and college
- Boston College: The Preparatory School, 1900-1901; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1900/01
- Boston College: The High School, 1901-1902; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1901/02
  High schools
- Boston College: The Law School, 1936-1973; 29 item(s) Announcements for 1936/37-1940/41, 1950/51-1956/57 Catalogs for 1941/42-1942/43, 1944, 1945/46-1948/49 Bulletins for 1957/58-1958/59, 1960/61-1963/64, 1965/66, 1967/68, 1970/71, 1972/73
  Law schools
- Boston College: School of Social Work, 1936-1969; 25 item(s) Announcements for 1936/37-1941/42, 1944/45-1953/54, 1955/56-1968/69
  - Boston College School of Social Work, [1940]; 1 item(s) Brochure on School of Social Work from c. 1940
- Boston College: College of Business Administration, 1939-1969; 23 item(s) Catalogs for 1939/40-1941/42, 1944/45-1945/46, 1949/50, 1952/53-1968/69
  Business schools
- Boston College: Graduate School, 1944-1961; 8 item(s) Announcements for 1944/45, 1949/50-1952/53, 1956/57 Catalogs for 1958/59, 1960/61
- Boston College: Evening College of Arts and Sciences (& Business Administration) Intown, 1945-1959; 4 item(s) Catalogs for 1952/53, 1956/57-1958/59 Catalog supplement in Business Administration 1945/46
  Evening and continuation schools
- Boston College: Summer Session, 1946-1976; 14 item(s) Bulletins for 1946-1947, 1949, 1966-1968, 1970-1976 Preliminary Announcement for 1966
- Boston College: College of Arts and Sciences, 1948-1970; 17 item(s) Catalogs for 1948-50, 1951/52-1955/56, 1957/58-1958/59, 1960/61-1966/67, 1969/70
- Boston College: The School of Nursing, 1953-1955; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1953-1954/55
  Nursing schools
- Boston College: Graduate School of Business Administration, 1960-1965; 2 item(s) Bulletins for 1960/61, 1963/65
- Boston College: The School of Education, 1960-1967; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1960/61, 1962/64, 1966/67
- Boston College: Graduate School Department of Education, [1960]; 1 item(s) Brochure on Graduate Course leading to Degree of Master of Education in Peripatology
- This is Boston College: Boston College Entrance Bulletin, 1962; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1962
- Boston College: The School of Management, 1970-1973; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1970/71-1971/73 Interim bulletin for Graduate Division for 1970/71
- Boston College: Graduate School of Arts & Sciences, 1970-1973; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1970/71-1972/73
- Boston College: Undergraduate Admissions Information, 1973-1977; 2 item(s) Bulletins for 1973/74 & 1976/77